Alice Recknagel Ireys Papers, 1885-2001
Sophia Smith Collection
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS (ROLLED DRAWINGS)
  - IV. MISCELLANEOUS PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
    - Consultations: Brooklyn Parks Department, proposed tree planting planundated (Roll Roll 16)